Bart-Jan Boverhof

January 2021

Utrecht, the Netherlands

bjboverhof@gmail.com | Personal Website | GitHub

EDUCATION

MSc Methodology and Statistics for the Behavioural, Biomedical and Social Sciences

Utrecht University

2019-Present

Master thesis: The Realtime Assessment of Workload by Means of Multiple Bio-Signals

BSc Sociology

Utrecht University

2016-2019

Bachelor-thesis: The Hidden Markov model: Practical guidelines

EXPERIENCE

• Utrecht University

Internship ASReview

Deep-learning programmer at ASReview: Active learning for systematic reviews

May 2021 - Present

Utrecht University

Student Assistant ESRA 2021

Local organization of the ninth edition of the European Survey Research Association conference

February 2021 - Present

Utrecht University

Student Assistant BigSurv20

Local organization of the second edition of the Big-Surv20 conference - Where Big Data Meets Survey Science

February 2020 - December 2020

National Institute for Public Health and the Environment - the Netherlands

Student Assistant EUPASMOS Project

Administrating interviews and instructing respondents participating in a study monitoring physical activity of the Dutch population

July 2018 - May 2019

ABOUT ME

I am Bart-Jan. I'm a graduate student of methods and statistics at Utrecht University. My interest mostly lies in machine-learning, or more specific, deep-learning. I highly enjoy to disentangle a certain subject. Statistical research lends itself perfectly for getting to the bottom of stuff. This rabbit-hole like nature implies that there is always something more. When you think you finally know it all, something new appears on the horizon.

SKILLS

Computer Skills

R, Python, LATEX, Mplus, Git(Hub) SPSS,

Programming Practices

Functional Programming, Object Oriented Programming, Deep-learning with PyTorch

Spoken Languages

Dutch (native), English, German

HOBBIES & INTERESTS









Hiking

Reading

Philosophy

Three Seven Nine One